Earth just got a little stranger.
Home is a fantasy, comedy, animation film directed by Tim Johnson.
When Earth is taken over by the overly-confident Boov, an alien race in search of a new place to call
home, all humans are promptly relocated, while all Boov get busy reorganizing the planet.
But when one resourceful girl, Tip, manages to avoid capture, she finds
herself the accidental accomplice of a banished Boov named Oh.
The two fugitives realize there’s a lot more at stake than intergalactic
relations as they embark on the road trip of a lifetime.
Oh (voice), played by Jim Parsons.
Gratuity 'Tip' Tucci (voice), played by Rihanna.
Capitain Smek (voice), played by Steve Martin.
Lucy Tucci (voice), played by Jennifer Lopez.
Kyle (voice), played by Matt Jones.
Gorg Commander / Father / Boov (voice), played by Brian Stepanek.
Home is a 2015 American animated science fiction comedy film produced by DreamWorks Animation
SKG, loosely based on the 2007 children's book The True Meaning of Smekday.
The film was directed by Tim Johnson, written by Tom J.
Astle and Matt Ember, and stars the voices of Jim Parsons,
Rihanna, Steve Martin, Jennifer Lopez, and Matt Jones.
The story follows the shared adventures of a friendly alien who is shunned by the rest of his kind, and a
teenage girl searching for her mother after they are separated during an invasion of Earth.
The film premiered at the Boulder International Film Festival on March 7, 2015,
and was released in theaters on March 27 by 20th Century Fox.
Home was promoted with the release of a prequel short film,
Almost Home, which was shown in theaters in 2014.
Rihanna created a concept album of the same name.
The soundtrack also includes guest vocals from Jennifer Lopez, among others, and was
supported by two singles, "Towards the Sun" and "Feel the Light".
Home received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $386
million worldwide against a $135 million budget.
A spin-off television series, Home: Adventures
with Tip & Oh, was released in 2016.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, villain, alien, space, alien invasion.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.